Guide to The American Pageant Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
The American Pageant Collection
1979-1998
SC0846
Ferrand-Andrew, Colleen, collector.
1 Linear feet
Collection includes the 6th (Vol. II only), 7th, 8th, 10th (Vol. II only) and 11th editions of THE AMERICAN PAGEANT: A HISTORY OF THE REPUBLIC by David M. Kennedy and Thomas Andrew Bailey; and the 4th edition of THE BRIEF AMERICAN PAGEANT by Kennedy, Bailey, and Mel Piehl.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Collection includes the 6th (Vol. II only), 7th, 8th, 10th (Vol. II only) and 11th editions of THE AMERICAN PAGEANT: A HISTORY OF THE REPUBLIC by David M. Kennedy and Thomas Andrew Bailey; and the 4th edition of THE BRIEF AMERICAN PAGEANT by Kennedy, Bailey, and Mel Piehl.
Access Terms
Ferrand-Andrew, Colleen, collector.; United States--History--Textbooks.
Collection Contents
- Bailey and Kennedy, The American Pageant
  - 6th edition Vol. II, paperback, 1979 (Box 1)
  - 7th edition Vol. I and II, paperback, 1983 (Box 1)
  - 8th edition, hardback, 1987 (Box 1)
  - 8th edition Vol. I, paperback, 1987 (Box 2)
  - 10th edition Vol. II, paperback, 1994 (Box 2)
- Bailey, Kennedy, Lizabeth Cohen, The American Pageant
  - 11th edition Vol. I and II, paperback, 1998 (Box 2)
- Kennedy, Bailey, and Mel Piehl, The Brief American Pageant
  - 4th edition, 1996 (Box 2)